Lesson 19  At the Museum
博物館で
学校の遠足で、町の博物館に行きました。
On a school trip, we visited the town museum.
入り口には、地元の画家が描いた大きな絵がありました。
At the entrance, a large picture
was painted by a local artist.
中に入ると、英語は世界中のたくさんの
国で話されていることを学びました。
Inside, we learned that English is spoken
in many countries around the world.
次の部屋には古い本がありました。
In the next room, there was an old book.
その本は多くの人に愛されています。
It is loved by many people.
毎年、たくさんの生徒に読まれています。
Every year, it is read by many students.
奥の部屋には、古いお城の模型がありました。
In the far room, there was
a model of an old castle.
「このお城は百年前に建てられたんです」
とガイドさんが教えてくれました。
“This castle was built hundred
years ago,” the guide told us.
外に出ると、うしろにそびえる山は町の
みんなに愛されているということでした。
When we went outside, the mountain behind
us was loved by everyone in the town.